Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Records, 1837 - 2013
Bentley Historical Library
- Director's Files, 1905-2013
  - Topical Files, 1980-2013
    - 2003-2013
      - Papers, Presentations, and Professional Meetings
        - Arcadia Lectures (United Kingdom), 2007; 2011; 3 folders (Box 295)
        - Asa Gray Talk, 2008 (Box 295)
        - Association of American Universities Chief Academic Officers, 2009 (Box 295)
        - Association for Library Collections & Technical Services (ALCTS) President's Program, 2011 (Box 295)
        - Bill Ayers Event, 2009 (Box 295)
        - Blackwell Conference, 2009 (Box 295)
        - Blue Ribbon Task Force, 2008-2010; 2 folders (Box 295)
        - Bowdoin College, 2012 (Box 295)
        - Business and Finance (University of Michigan) Presentation, 2011 (Box 295)
          (Discussion of Library as Domain Steward)
        - Business Insider Radio Interview, 2012 (Box 295)
        - Canadian Library Association, 2009-2010; 2 folders (Box 295)
        - Central Development Council Address, June 2008 (Box 297)
        - Charleston Conference, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Cooperative Collection Development Discussion Group (COLD), 2010 (Box 297)
        - Copyright Office, 2011 (Box 297)
        - CTN TV Segment on A2Fiber, 2010 (Box 297)
        - Digital Preservation Summit, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Digital Public Library of America (DPLA), 2012 (Box 297)
        - Economic Outlook Conference, 2008 (Box 297)
        - Educause ECAR Symposium, 2008; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Faculty Senate Presentation, 2009 (Box 297)
        - Fiftieth UM Reunion (Class of 1960), 2010 (Box 297)
        - Ford School of Public Policy Washington Panel, 2009 (Box 297)
        - Frye Leadership Webinar, 2010 (Box 297)
        - Gift Officer Training, 2010 (Box 297)
        - Goldman School of Public Policy, UC Berkeley External Review Committee, October 2010; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Google Books Settlement Conference (Columbia University), March 2009 (Box 297)
        - "HathiTrust, Google Books, and the Future of Research,", 2012 (Box 297)
          (Debate with John Unsworth at MIT)
        - Hewlett Foundation Community College Open Textbooks, January 2008 (Box 297)
        - House Science and Technology Roundtable, 2009 (Box 297)
        - John Seely Brown (JSB) Symposium, 2007-2008; 3 folders (Box 297)
        - Institute of Museum and Library Services, 2010 (Box 297)
        - International Conference on the Preservation of Digital Objects (iPRES), 2009 (Box 297)
        - IMS Global Learning Consortium Summit, 2008; 2012; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Israeli National Library, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Ithaka Sustainable Scholarship, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Kuali Days, November 2010; 3 folders (Box 297)
        - Library Technology Council, 2009 (Box 297)
        - Life2 Conference (UK), 2008 (Box 297)
        - Michigan Quarterly Review Symposium, May 2009 (Box 297)
        - Microsoft Faculty Summit, 2010 (Box 297)
        - Minnesota Strategic Planning, 2009 (Box 297)
        - National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER), 2008 (Box 297)
        - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (NCLIS), 2007 (Box 297)
        - National Science Foundation Open Access Repository Feasibility, January 2010 (Box 297)
        - New York Law School Google Settlement Conference, 2009 (Box 297)
        - "Online Humanities Scholarship, The Shape of Things to Come", March 2010 (Box 297)
          (Sponsored by Mellon Foundation and University of Virginia.)
        - Ontario Library Association Superconference, February 2012 (Box 297)
        - Property Tax Policy Roundtable, 2008-2009; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Public Goods Units, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Questioning Authority Conference, March 2008 (Box 297)
        - Radcliffe National Digital Library Workshop, 2010 (Box 297)
        - Rotary Club, 2009; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Scholarly Communications Institute (SCI), 2008; 2011; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - School of Art and Design (A&D) Faculty, undated (Box 297)
        - Shanghai Jiao Toing University, 2008; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Shared Library Initiatives Workshop, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Sloan Advisory Board, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Social Protest Panel, 2008 (Box 297)
        - St. John's Bible Event, 2012 (Box 297)
        - Syracuse University Accreditation Evaluation, 2008 (Box 297)
        - TEDx, 2011 (Box 297)
        - "Tower and Cloud" Podcast, February 2009 (Box 297)
        - Union College, 2008 (Box 297)
        - University of California, Berkely New Directions Presentation, December 2007 (Box 297)
        - University of Washington, 2011; 2 folders (Box 297)
        - University Publishing Roundtable, 2008 (Box 297)
        - Vice Provosts and Associate Deans, 2011 (Box 297)
        - Windsor Castle Consultation, 2007-2008; 3 folders (Box 297)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG), 2008; 3 folders (Box 297)
      - School of Education, 2007-2008; 2 folders (Box 297)
        (Includes records on instruction with rich media and the Dean's Advisory Council)
      - School of Information (SI), 2008; 4 folders (Box 297)
      - University Library Administration
        - Author's Forum: Akpan, Uwem, 2009 (Box 297)
        - Digital Media Commons (Duderstadt Center)
          - Budgets and Budget Plans, 2006-2008 (Box 298)
          - Correspondence and Associated Materials, 2007-2008 (Box 298)
            (Includes Digital Media Commons-Duderstadt Transition Plan, space usage, facilities, and other issues)
          - CTools Implementation and Usage, 2007 (Box 298)
          - Furniture Plans, 2006 (Folder 1)
          - Library/DMC Leadership Meeting, September 2009 (Box 298)
          - Reports, 2007-2008 (Box 298)
        - Events, 2010-2011; 5 folders (Box 298)
        - Library Dean's Group, 2010-2011; 2 folders (Box 298)
        - Library Updates, 2008-2012; 11 folders (Box 298)
        - Martin Luther King Day, 2010 (Box 298)
        - Meetings
          - Reference, 2012 (Box 298)
          - Technical Services (TS), 2011 (Box 298)
        - Promotion Review Committee (PRC), 2009 (Box 298)
        - Reorganization, 2013 (Box 298)
        - Reports
          - Library Leadership Roles within the University (Draft), undated (Box 298)
          - Scholarly Publishing Office Year End Report, 2009 (Box 298)
          - Summon Benefit Analysis, 2011 (Box 298)
        - Retiree Reception, 2009 (Box 298)
      - University Library Leadership Council, 2008-2013 (Box 298)
      - University of Michigan Press Executive Committee, 2013 (Box 298)
      - Video Content Management (University of Michigan), 2013 (Box 298)
  - Annual Reports, 1947-1953
    The Annual Reports subseries of the Director's Office subgroup consists of two types of annual reports: annual reports from the various library units to the library director, and the director's summary annual report sent to the president of the university. Arranged chronologically, these reports document the years 1947 to 1977. Both types of reports for additional years can be found within the various directors' office files. Moreover, a complete run of the library director's annual report to the president of the university can be found in the bound volumes of the President's Report for the period 1853 to 1984 (consult Bentley Historical Library Printed Works Catalog).
    - 1965-1977 (Box 154)
    - 1947-1953, 6 folders (Box 161)
  - Budget Files, 1995/96-2003/04
    The Budget Files series contains a variety of budget requests and reports. The series is broken down into several sub sub-series according to fiscal year from 1995/96 to 2003/04. Files are arranged alphabetically within each sub sub-series. Included are personnel and non-personnel fund reports, grant reports, hourly budget reports and University Library budget request materials.
    - 1995-1996
      - General Funds Report (Box 268)
      - Hourly Budget Reports (Box 268)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 268)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports (Box 268)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 268)
    - 1996-1997
      - General (Box 268)
      - Hourly Budget Reports (Box 268)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 268)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports, 4 folders (Box 268)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 268)
    - 1997-1998
      - General, 3 folders (Box 268)
      - Hourly Budget Reports (Box 268)
      - Long-Range Planning Academic and Budget Planning Meeting (Box 268)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 269)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports, 4 folders (Box 269)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 269)
    - 1998-1999
      - General, 3 folders (Box 269)
      - Business and Finance (Box 269)
      - Hourly Budget Reports (Box 269)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports, 2 folders (Box 269)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 269)
      - Request (Box 269)
    - 1999-2000
      - General, 3 folders (Box 270)
      - Business and Finance (Box 270)
      - Collections and Budget (Box 270)
      - Commitments (Box 270)
      - Equipment (Box 270)
      - Hourly Budget Reports (Box 270)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 270)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports, 3 folders (Box 270)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 270)
    - 2000-2001
      - General (Box 270)
      - Commitments (Box 270)
      - Equipment (Box 270)
      - Hourly Budget Reports, 2 folders (Box 271)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 271)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports, 2 folders (Box 271)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 271)
      - Photoduplication (Box 271)
      - Request, 2 folders (Box 271)
    - 2001-2002
      - General (Box 271)
      - Book Funds (Box 271)
      - Business and Finance (Box 271)
      - Commitments (Box 271)
      - Grants (Box 271)
      - Hourly Budget Reports, 2 folders (Box 271)
      - Library Fines (Box 271)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 271)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports, 2 folders (Box 272)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 272)
      - Request, 3 folders (Box 272)
    - 2002-2003
      - General (Box 272)
      - Commitments (Box 272)
      - Finance and Facilities (Box 272)
      - Hourly Budget Reports (Box 272)
      - Non-General Funds and Grants Budget Reports (Box 272)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports (Box 272)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 272)
      - Request (Box 272)
    - 2003-2004
      - General (Box 273)
      - Cassidy Fund (Box 273)
      - Commitments (Box 273)
      - Finance and Facilities (Box 273)
      - Heyns Fund (Box 273)
      - Non-Personnel Budget Reports (Box 273)
      - Personnel Budget Reports (Box 273)
      - Request, 3 folders (Box 273)
- Associate Director for Technical Services, 1979-1986
  Another member of the senior administrative team, the Associate Director for Technical Services has primary responsibility for maintaining bibliographic architecture and providing remote and on-site access in a variety of formats. The Associate Director for Technical Services Files (William Gosling), 1984-1997 (7.0 linear feet) document the tenure of William Gosling, who was later appointed interim director of the University Library in 1997 and then director in 1998. Gosling's files detail the implementation of MIRLYN and the management and licensing of other databases. The records also document preservation initiatives, acquisitions, and relationships with state and national organizations.
  - Topical Files
    - 1979-1986
      - Anglo-American Cataloguing Rules, 2nd. ed. (Box 156)
      - Associate Director's Council, 1983; 1985 (Box 156)
      - Automated Systems
        - Geac Corp. On-line Circulation System (Box 156)
        - INNOVative Interfaces Inc. ACQuisition System (Box 156)
        - Integrated Library System
          - AD Council (Box 156)
          - Planning Documents (Box 156)
        - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC) (Box 156)
        - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN)
          - General (Box 156)
          - Acquisitions (Box 156)
      - Budget, 1981-1985; 4 folders (Box 156)
      - Buhr (Box 156)
      - Collection Development
        - General (Box 156)
        - Collection Analysis Project (CAP)
          - Final Reports (Box 156)
          - Retreat (Box 156)
        - Purchasing Approval Plans (Box 156)
      - Gerontology Library (Box 157)
      - Gifts (Box 157)
      - Planning, 1979-1986; 6 folders (Box 157)
      - Preservation
        - General (Box 157)
        - Grant Proposals (Box 157)
      - Retrospective Conversion
        - General (Box 157)
        - Conversion of Serials (Box 157)
      - Space Allocations in the Graduate Library (Box 157)
      - Task Force
        - On Incomplete Separates (Box 157)
        - On the Official Catalog (Box 157)
- Assistant Director for Technical Services Files, 1984-1999
  The Assistant Director for Technical Services Files, 1984-1999, are the files of William Gosling. The crux of these files focuses on matters of concern relating to the technical services functions of the university library including cataloging policies. The Subgroup consists of a Topical File divided into two chronological spans covering the years 1984-1991 and 194-1996.
  - Topical Files, 1984-1996
    - 1984-1991
      - Acquisitions, 1987-1990 (Box 203)
      - Administrative Services, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - Area Programs, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - Asia Library, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - Bindery, 1985-1989 (Box 203)
      - Buhr Building, 1986-1989 (Box 203)
      - Business Administration Library, 1989 (Box 203)
      - Cataloging Policy Council, 1984-1990 (Box 203)
      - Classed Separates, 1986 (Box 203)
      - Clements Library, 1987-1988 (Box 203)
      - Collection Management, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - Center for Research Libraries (CRL), 1989 (Box 203)
      - Correspondence, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 203)
      - Database Administration, 1986-1989 (Box 203)
      - Director, 1988-1989 (Box 203)
      - Dissertations, 1988-1989 (Box 203)
      - Documents, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - 18th Century Short Title Catalog, 1989 (Box 203)
      - Engineering Library., 1987-1988 (Box 203)
      - Exchange and Gift Operations, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - Report, 1980 (Box 203)
      - Goals, 1986-1988 (Box 203)
      - Grants, 1986-1989 (Box 203)
      - Information and Technology Division (ITD), 1989 (Box 203)
      - Interlibrary Loan, 1989 (Box 203)
      - Law Library, 1988-1989 (Box 203)
      - Library Catalogs, 1986 (Box 203)
      - Library of Congress, 1987-1989 (Box 203)
      - Library of Michigan, 1989 (Box 203)
      - Management, 1982 (Box 203)
      - Medical Library 1986-189 (Box 204)
      - Medical Subject Headings, 1989 (Box 204)
      - Monographic Cataloging, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 204)
      - Music Cataloging, 1986-1989 (Box 204)
      - National Coordinated Cataloging Project (NCCP), 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 204)
      - National Information Standards Organization, 1987 (Box 204)
      - NOTIS, 1988 (Box 204)
      - OCLC, 1987-1989
        - Association for Library Information (AFLI), 1986-1989 (Box 204)
      - Preservation, 1988-1990 (Box 204)
      - Rare Books Cataloging, 1987-1989 (Box 204)
      - Retrospective Conversion (Recon), 1985-1989; 2 folders (Box 204)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG)
        - Bibtech, 1987-1988 (Box 204)
        - Budget, 1987-1989 (Box 204)
        - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Science (ICPSR), 1986-1989 (Box 204)
        - Preservation, 1989 (Box 204)
        - RLIN-CJK System, 1983-1986 (Box 204)
        - RLIN Search Guidelines, 1988 (Box 204)
        - Retrospective Conversion, 1987-1989 (Box 204)
        - Searches, 1989 (Box 204)
      - Rosenthal Endowment, 1988-1989 (Box 204)
      - Selectors, 1986 (Box 204)
      - Serials, 1986-1990 (Box 204)
      - Serial Budget Cuts, 1987-1988 (Box 204)
      - Short Title Catalog (STC), 1988 (Box 204)
      - Slide Cataloging, 1986-1987 (Box 204)
      - South Asia Library, 1986-1987 (Box 204)
      - Systems, 1987-1990 (Box 204)
      - Technical Services
        - Budget, 1985 (Box 204)
        - General, 1987-1989 (Box 204)
        - Technical Services Manual (Box 204)
        - Technical Services Memoranda, 2 folders (Box 204)
        - Unit Heads Meetings, 1977-1991; 7 folders (Box 204)
      - University Microfilms Incorporated (UMI), 1987-1989 (Box 204)
      - Utlas, 1987-1989 (Box 204)
      - Withdrawals, 1988 (Box 204)
    - 1984-1996
      (Gosling)
      - Acquisitions, 1986-1992 (Box 222)
      - Africana, 1992-1994 (Box 222)
      - Annual Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 222)
      - Area Programs, 1990-1994 (Box 222)
      - Asia Library, 1990-1994 (Box 222)
      - Atkins, Dan, 1991-1992 (Box 222)
      - "Austin Report" (Problem MIRLYN Records), 1993-1994 (Box 222)
      - Binding, 1990-1994 (Box 222)
      - Book Sales, 1990-1994 (Box 222)
      - Brief Record Cataloging, 1984-1987 (Box 222)
      - Buhr (Storage facility), 1988-1994 (Box 222)
      - Business/Finance, 1992-1994 (Box 222)
      - Cataloging Policy Council, 1987-1994; 2 folders (Box 222)
      - CD-Rom-Local area Network, 1991-1992 (Box 222)
      - Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (CAAS), 1991 (Box 222)
      - Center for Information Technology Experimentation (CITE), 1992-1993 (Box 222)
      - Chadwyck-Healey, 1987; 1991 (Box 222)
      - CIESIN, 1993-1994 (Box 222)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General, 1990-1996; 2 folders (Box 222)
        - Academy Publications (Microfilming Grant), 1994 (Box 222)
        - Grant #3, 1993 (Box 222)
        - Grant II-A (Virtual Library, PAC Link), 1993-1994 (Box 222)
        - Preservation, 1986-1994; 2 folders (Box 222)
      - Collection Management, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 223)
      - Connector, 1993 (Box 223)
      - CONSER (Conservation of Serials), 1987; 1996 (Box 223)
      - Contracts, 1990 (Box 223)
      - Copyright, 1990-1994 (Box 223)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box 223)
      - Database Administration, 1990-1993 (Box 223)
      - Dean, 1991-1994 (Box 223)
      - Dissertations, 1990-1993 (Box 223)
      - Documents, 190-1993 (Box 223)
      - Exchange and Gifts, 1992-1993 (Box 223)
      - Faxon, 1990-1992 (Box 223)
      - Ford Motor Company Technical Information Center, 1993-1994 (Box 223)
      - Forum (Librarian's Forum), 1991-1994 (Box 223)
      - Gopher, 1992-1994 (Box 223)
      - Grants, 1990-1994 (Box 223)
      - Information Technology Division (ITD), 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 223)
      - Inter-University Consortium for Political Science Research (ICPSR), 1989-1992 (Box 223)
      - Labadie II-C (Processing Labadie Serials Grant), 1990-1995 (Box 223)
      - Library of Congress, 1990-1992 (Box 223)
      - Luce Foundation (Vietnamese Union Catalog), 1987-1991 (Box 224)
      - Maps, 1991-1992 (Box 224)
      - MARC Holdings Task Force, 1991 (Box 224)
      - MathSci Database, 1990-1993 (Box 224)
      - Medical Subject Headings/Medline, 1990-1991 (Box 224)
      - Michigan Cooperative, 1992 (Box 224)
      - Michigan Library Consortium, 1990 (Box 224)
      - Microforms, 1986; 1990 (Box 224)
      - MIRLYN (Michigan Research Library Information Network)
        - General, 1985-1994; 5 folders (Box 224)
        - Assumptions, 1986-1987 (Box 224)
        - Barcodes, 1989-1990 (Box 224)
        - Bibliographic File, 1987-1988 (Box 224)
        - Circulation, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 224)
        - Contract, 1985-1988 (Box 224)
        - Equipment, 1987-1991 (Box 224)
        - GEAC, 1986-1989 (Box 224)
        - Holding Record, 1987-1988; 1991 (Box 224)
        - Implementation, 1985-1989 (Box 224)
        - Implementation Team, 1986-1989 (Box 224)
        - MathSci Database, 1989 (Box 224)
        - Public Service Council (PSC), 1987-1990 (Box 224)
        - RLIN (Research Library Network), 1987-1988 (Box 224)
        - Serials Acquisition, 1987-1990 (Box 225)
        - Tapeloading, 1988-1990 (Box 225)
        - Terminals, 1987-1989 (Box 225)
        - Training, 1987-1988 (Box 225)
        - Use, 1988-1993 (Box 225)
        - Use of MIRLYN by other Campus Libraries, 1985-1991 (Box 225)
      - Monograph Cataloging, 1986-1992 (Box 225)
      - MRLT (Michigan Research Library Triangle)
        - General, 1992-1997; 6 folders (Box 225)
        - Modern Language Association (MLA) File, 1995-1997 (Box 225)
        - PACLink Implementation Project, 1993-1994 (Box 225)
        - Steering Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 225)
      - Multiple Versions Task Force, 1992 (Box 225)
      - Music, 1991-1994 (Box 225)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Preservation Grant, 1988-1993 (Box 225)
      - NOTIS, 1987-1994; 2 folders (Box 226)
      - OCLC, 1990-1993; 3 folders (Box 226)
      - OCLC Budget, 1993 (Box 226)
      - Ohio State University Gateway Project, 1992-1993 (Box 226)
      - Other Libraries
        - Bentley Library, 1992-1996 (Box 226)
        - Clements Library, 1991-1996 (Box 226)
        - Dearborn Campus, 1990-1996 (Box 226)
        - Flint Campus, 1991-1996 (Box 226)
        - Ford Presidential Library, 1994 (Box 226)
        - Kresge Business Administration Library, 1989-1996 (Box 226)
        - Law Library, 1995-1997 (Box 226)
      - Papyrology, 1987; 1991-1992 (Box 226)
      - Planning, 1989-1991 (Box 226)
      - Preservation, 1984-1987; 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 226)
      - Public Health (Axelrod Collection), 1993 (Box 227)
      - Public Services, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Publications, 1991-1995 (Box 227)
      - Questionnaires (Completed Surveys), 1990-1994 (Box 227)
      - Reallocation Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 227)
      - RELICS (Renaissance Liturgical Imprints Census) Database, 1992-1993 (Box 227)
      - Retrospective Conversion Project (Kellogg Foundation), 1988-1994 (Box 227)
      - Research Library Group (RLG)
        - General, 1990-1994; 3 folders (Box 227)
        - Batch Reconversion and Preservation, 1990-1992 (Box 227)
        - Budget, 1989-1992; 1994; 2 folders (Box 227)
        - Preservation, 1987 (Box 227)
      - Serials
        - General, 1985-1992 (Box 227)
        - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 227)
      - Shelflist, 1991-1992 (Box 227)
      - Statistics, 1988-1994; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Systems, 1989-1992 (Box 228)
      - Taubman Medical Library, 1991-1993 (Box 228)
      - Technical Services, 1987-1994 (Box 228)
      - Technical Services Assistant to Assistant Director, 1993-1994 (Box 228)
      - Technical Services Directors of Large Research Libraries Discussion Group (TSDLRLDG), 1990-1994 (Box 228)
      - Techlink, 1991-1993 (Box 228)
      - Transportation History Grant (Railroad Collections), 1993-1994 (Box 228)
      - TULIP (The University Licensing Program)/Elsevier Electronic Journals, 1991-1996; 6 folders (Box 228)
      - University Microfilms (UMI), 1990-1994 (Box 228)
      - University Press, 1994 (Box 228)
      - Versions Committee, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 228)
      - Ward and Associates, 1989-1992 (Box 228)
      - Washtenaw Livingston Library Network (WLLN), 1993-1994 (Box 228)
    - 1981-1999
      (Gosling/Warner)
      The 1981-1999 series (3.0 linear feet) of the Assistant Director for Technical Services Files (William Gosling/Beth Warner) includes materials from the AD for Technical Services tenures of William Gosling and Beth Warner. The series also includes a small amount of Gosling's correspondence related to technical services issues while interim director and then director of the library.
      - Blackwell Table of Contents, 1995-1999 (Box 246)
      - Book Sale, 1993-1998 (Box 246)
      - Buhr, 1987-1999 (Box 246)
      - Business and Finance, 1995-1996 (Box 246)
      - Cabinet, 1996-1999 (Box 246)